celebrateexpress.com 2017-06-28

# BirthdayExpress

## Do you have a security guarantee?

Yes, we take your business seriously and use every precaution necessary to ensure that your shopping experience is safe and exciting! We use the best technology available, Secure Socket Layer encrypting, to keep your private and credit card information as secure as possible. 

## How can I remove my name from your mailing list?

Follow the instructions below to remove yourself from any of our mailing lists:

### Our Email Lists

On our [email preferences page](https://www.birthdayexpress.com/profile/footeroremailunsub), enter your email and select the "I do not wish to receive any e-mails from Birthday Express" option. 

#### What is your privacy policy?

Last Updated: February 21, 2012   
Effective Date: February 26, 2012.  

We at Birthday Express value your business and trust. Therefore, we will not sell, rent, or give away any customers' e-mail address to other businesses. We request your e-mail address so we can send you important information regarding your order (order confirmation, order processing, and tracking number). We may e-mail you coupons or discount offers in the future. We may also share information we collect at our site with other members of the BUYSEASONS family (the Birthday Express website is owned by BUYSEASONS, Inc.). They may use this information to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you. 

Our sites track information about the visits to each site. For example, statistics are compiled that show the daily number of visitors to the site, the daily requests received for particular files on the site, and from what countries those requests come. We may also track information about our users browsing activity as they navigate through our site. These statistics are used to customize our Web site to better meet your needs and may also be provided to others, but we will not provide any personally identifiable information that may be associated with those statistics to any third parties.

If you supply us with your address online you may receive periodic mailings letting you know about new products and services. If you do not wish to receive these mailings, contact us and we’ll remove you from our list. 

If you have placed an order with our company, we may share your mailing address with other reputable companies. We do this so that you can receive mailings and offers from those companies for products or services we think you might like. However, if you would like to have your name put on our do-not-share list, please contact us and we’ll update this information so you don’t receive future mailings.

We may allow third-parties, including our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies or web beacons, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies ([networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)). You may also limit the information collected by managing cookies on your computer or through your preferred web browser and related programs. Information on how to do so may be found a networkadvertising.com. 

We limit access to personally identifiable information to a select number of employees who are committed to our privacy and security policies, and who need access to the information in order to perform their jobs. 

We collect personal information such as full names, addresses, e-mail addresses, etc, when it's voluntarily given to us by our customers. We do ask parents/guardians for children's birth month and year information so we can send a Birthday Express catalog during that time for party planning.

We also collect payment information so that we can bill our customers for their orders. To complete business transactions, credit card numbers are verified by a qualified financial institution before the order is shipped. So our customers know the status of their order, we’ll send them confirmation emails that provides the order information.

If you no longer wish to receive promotional emails or catalogs from us click here for directions on how to remove your name from our lists. Online contests and sweepstakes may have different rules regarding contact information so please refer to the individual guidelines posted for each promotion

To update any of your contact information send an e-mail with the revised information to [service@birthdayexpress.com](mailto://service@birthdayexpress.com). 

Customers who have given their telephone number online may receive a call from us with information regarding your order. When providing your telephone number, please provide both the area code and phone number. Your phone number will not be shared with anyone.

We occasionally make portions of our mailing list available to carefully screened companies whose products may interest you. If you do not want your name made available - or if you have moved, are receiving duplicate catalogs or would prefer not to receive catalogs from us - send an e-mail to [service@birthdayexpress.com](mailto://service@birthdayexpress.com). If you would like to remove your name from all mailing lists, visit [DMAChoice Direct Marketing Association](http://www.dmachoice.org/), at [www.dmachoice.org](http://www.dmachoice.org/) for more information.

If you choose to post a product review, we will display your chosen user name and any additional identifying information that you agree for us to post, including but not limited to age, location, and gender. Any personally identifiable information that you submit as part of the review can be read or used by other visitors to the Site. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review. 

From time to time, we may be required to disclose customer information in response to requests from law-enforcement officials conducting investigations; subpoenas; a court order; or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law. We also will release personal information where disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights, enforce our , Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect ourselves or others. 

### Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of California, in addition to the rights set forth above, you have the right to request information from us regarding the manner in which we share certain categories of personal information, if any, with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. California law gives you the right to send us a request at a designated address to receive the following information: 

  * the categories of information we disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year
  * the names and addresses of the third parties that received that information; and
  * if the nature of the third party's business cannot be determined from their name, examples of the products or services marketed.

We may provide this information in a standardized format that is not specific to you. The designated email address for these requests is [service@birthdayexpress.com](mailto:service@birthdayexpress.com). 

This Policy was last changed on February 21, 2012 with an effective date of February 26, 2012. If we make changes to any terms or conditions of the Policy, the changes will be posted on this portion of the Sites so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, to whom we will disclose it and what choices you have. Any change, modification, addition or removal of portions of this Policy will be announced on our Sites and/or via email at least five (5) business days before it is implemented. Please be sure to check this page before proceeding to use any of our Sites. 

If you have questions about our privacy policy, contact us at:

  * Customer Service
  * Birthday Express
  * 5915 South Moorland Road
  * New Berlin, WI 53151

### What is the Birthday Express Terms of Use policy?

For the complete details for our Terms of Use and other agreements, click here.
